export const Quizzes = [[{
    question: "Which one of the below doesn't represent a cryptography algorithm? ",
    optionA: "RSA",
    optionB: "KRS",
    optionC: "DSA",
    optionD: "DES",
    answer: "B"
},
{
    question: "How many keys are used in asymmetric cryptography?",
    optionA: "1",
    optionB: "2",
    optionC: "3",
    optionD: "4",
    answer: "B"
}],
[{
    question: "Which mode of operation for a block cipher has the characteristic that each possible block of plaintext has a defined corresponding ciphertext value and vice versa?",
    optionA: "Footprinting",
    optionB: "Hash function",
    optionC: "Watermark",
    optionD: "Electronic code book",
    answer: "D"
},
{
    question: "In password protection, what is the name of a random string of data used to modify a password hash called?",
    optionA: "Sheep dip",
    optionB: "Salt",
    optionC: "Bypass",
    optionD: "Dongle",
    answer: "B"
},
{
    question: "Which cryptography approach is most often used by today's internet businesses and users?",
    optionA: "Public key infrastructure",
    optionB: "Output feedback",
    optionC: "Encrypting File System",
    optionD: "Single sign-on",
    answer: "A"
},
{
    question: "What is the name of the issuer of public key infrastructure certificates?",
    optionA: "Man in the middle",
    optionB: "Certificate authority",
    optionC: "Resource Access Control Facility",
    optionD: "Script kiddie",
    answer: "B"
}],
[{
    question: "Which of the following was not a final contender in NIST's assessment of Data Encryption Standard, or DES, replacements?",
    optionA: "MARS",
    optionB: "RC6",
    optionC: "Rijndael",
    optionD: "Blowfish",
    answer: "D"
},
{
    question: "Which encryption algorithm supplanted DES?",
    optionA: "Rijndael",
    optionB: "Kerberos",
    optionC: "Blowfish",
    optionD: "IPsec",
    answer: "A"
},
{
    question: "What is a trial-and-error method used to decode encrypted data through exhaustive effort rather than employing intellectual strategies?",
    optionA: "Chaffing and winnowing",
    optionB: "Cryptanalysis",
    optionC: "Serendipity",
    optionD: "Brute-force cracking",
    answer: "D"
},
{
    question: "What is the inclusion of a secret message in otherwise unencrypted text or images called?",
    optionA: "Masquerade",
    optionB: "Steganography",
    optionC: "Spoof",
    optionD: "Eye-in-hand system",
    answer: "B"
},
{
    question: "What is the Diffie-Hellman key exchange vulnerable to?",
    optionA: "Snooping",
    optionB: "Man-in-the-middle attacks",
    optionC: "ROBOT attacks",
    optionD: "Phishing attacks",
    answer: "B"
},
],
[{
    question: "What is a widely used privacy-ensuring program by individuals and corporations?",
    optionA: "Digital Signature Standard",
    optionB: "Online Certificate Status Protocol",
    optionC: "Secure HTTP",
    optionD: "Pretty Good Privacy",
    answer: "D"
},
{
    question: "Until when will 2,048-bit RSA keys be sufficient?",
    optionA: "2025",
    optionB: "2030",
    optionC: "2040",
    optionD: "Forever",
    answer: "B"
},
{
    question: "What is the name of the encryption/decryption key known only to the party or parties that exchange secret messages?",
    optionA: "E-signature",
    optionB: "Digital certificate",
    optionC: "Private key",
    optionD: "Security token",
    answer: "C"
},
{
    question: "Which of the following was commonly used in cryptography during World War II?",
    optionA: "Tunneling",
    optionB: "Personalization",
    optionC: "Van Eck phreaking",
    optionD: "One-time pad",
    answer: "D"
},
{
    question: "How long would a 10-bit message be after being encrypted by a stream cipher?",
    optionA: "2 bits",
    optionB: "5 bits",
    optionC: "10 bits",
    optionD: "20 bits",
    answer: "C"
}
]
]